export const questionData ={
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Complete this statement “Holding the mystery of the faith in a pure",
      "options": [
        "Foundation",
        "Conscience",
        "Understanding",
        "Walk with God."
      ],
      "answer": "Conscience"
    },
    {
      "question": "All these are descriptions of faith except",
      "options": [
        "The currency of believers",
        "The pillar of salvation",
        "The anchor of salvation",
        "The rock of ages"
      ],
      "answer": "The anchor of salvation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Another name for the fruits of the spirit is",
      "options": [
        "Benefits",
        "Results",
        "Blessings",
        "Advantageous"
      ],
      "answer": "Results"
    },
    {
      "question": "Atheists means",
      "options": [
        "people that deny existence of God",
        "people that neither believe in nor support God",
        "people in support of God",
        "people of other religions"
      ],
      "answer": "people that deny existence of God"
    },
    {
      "question": "People who believe in the existence of many gods and consult with them based on peculiar need are called",
      "options": [
        "Atheists",
        "Polytheists",
        "Antrotheists",
        "Pro theists"
      ],
      "answer":"Polytheists"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is our God?",
      "options": [
        "uncreated creator",
        "created creator",
        "uncreated noncreator",
        "created noncreator"
      ],
      "answer": "uncreated creator"
    },
    {
      "question": "Every Christian must believe and declare boldly that our God is",
      "options": [
        "Many Gods",
        "Only God",
        "Unique God",
        "God of Europe"
      ],
      "answer": "Unique God"
    },
    {
      "question": "The topic for lesson one is?",
      "options": [
        "Keys to knowing God",
        "Doctrine of the Trinity",
        "Who is our GOD?",
        "Political dominion"
      ],
      "answer": "who is our GOD?"
    },
    {
      "question": "The Apostle Paul expressed his desire to truly know God, this can be seen in",
      "options": [
        "Philippians 4:10",
        "Philippians 3:10",
        "Philippians 2:10",
        "Philippians 1:10"
      ],
      "answer" : "Philippians 3:10"
    },
    {
      "question": "According to lesson 2, Apostle Paul discovered the ______ of the Athens",
      "options": [
        "Glorious tendencies",
        "Apostolic tendencies",
        "Idolatrous tendencies",
        "Divine tendencies"
      ],
      "answer": "Idolatrous tendencies"
    },
    {
      "question": "If we genuinely hunger and thirst to know God, He will reveal Himself to us.",
      "options": [
        "True",
        "False",
        "None of the above",
        "A-C"
      ],
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "The doctrine of the trinity is Christianity’s most unique, defining, and awesome ____",
      "options": [
        "Trinity",
        "Mystery",
        "Theory",
        "Doctrine"
      ],
      "answer" : "Doctrine"
    },
    {
      "question": "The Phenomenon whereby people believe in three Gods is called",
      "options": [
        "Trinity",
        "Tritheism",
        "Tripoism",
        "Trinitancy"
      ],
      "answer": "Tritheism"
    },
    {
      "question": "Fasting is also spiritual sacrifices that aid the believer’s _______?",
      "options": [
        "Prayer",
        "Faith",
        "Sacrifice",
        "Sanctification"
      ],
      "answer": "Prayer"
    },
    {
      "question": "Spiritual sacrifices are part of the Christian’s worship and must be offered on God’s term i.e. it must be _____?",
      "options": [
        "Honour",
        "Sanctified",
        "Acceptable",
        "Justified"
      ],
      "answer": "Acceptable"
    },
    {
      "question": "Lesson 5 Bible passage is",
      "options": [
        "Philippians 4:8-9",
        "Philippians 3:8-9",
        "Philippians 5:8-9",
        "Philippians 4:2-7"
      ],
      "answer":"Philippians 4:8-9"
    },
    {
      "question": "Righteous living makes you a partner with?",
      "options": [
        "Jesus Christ",
        "Holy Spirit",
        "Almighty God",
        "Trinity"
      ],
      "answer": "Almighty God"
    },
    {
      "question": "Righteousness reveals genuine_______",
      "options": [
        "Sanctification",
        "Justification",
        "Salvation",
        "Devotion"
      ],
      "answer": "Salvation"
    },
    {
      "question": "The evidence of the overflow of Holy Spirit in the life of a believer is known as",
      "options": [
        "Speaking in parable",
        "Speaking mystery",
        "Speaking in theology",
        "Speaking in an unknown tongue"
      ],
      "answer": "Speaking in an unknown tongue"
    },
    {
      "question": "Benefits of speaking in tongues are the following except",
      "options": [
        "Improve prayer life",
        "Yield tongues to God",
        "Self-edification",
        "Acquire new language"
      ],
      "answer": "Acquire new language"
    },
    {
      "question": "Everyone including Christians have the right to life and liberty",
      "options": [
        "False",
        "True",
        "None of the above",
        "Neither false nor true"
      ],
      "answer": "True"
    },
    {
      "question": "Everyone is entitled to human rights without",
      "options": [
        "Violation",
        "Abuse",
        "Discrimination",
        "Assault"
      ],
      "answer":"Discrimation"
    },
    {
      "question": "Rule or Power over means?",
      "options": [
        "Authority",
        "Governance",
        "Dominion",
        "Leadership"
      ],
      "answer": "Dominion"
    },
    {
      "question": "______ Stole the key of dominion in the garden of Eden",
      "options": [
        "Devils",
        "Satan",
        "Eve",
        "Serpent"
      ],
      "answer": "Satan"
    },
    {
      "question": "Politics can be described as methodology and activities associated with running a",
      "options": [
        "Party",
        "Governor",
        "Party secretariat",
        "Government"
      ],
      "answer": "Government"
    },
    {
      "question": "The Bible passage for lesson 9 is?",
      "options": [
        "Nehemiah 6:14-19",
        "Nehemiah 7:14-19",
        "Nehemiah 5:14-19",
        "Nehemiah 4:14-19"
      ],
      "answer": "Nehemiah 5:14-19"
    },
    {
      "question": "Involvement in Politics will take one to Hell?",
      "options": [
        "True",
        "False",
        "A and B",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "Believers must be involved in politics",
      "options": [
        "True",
        "False",
        "None of the above",
        "A and B"
      ],
      "answer": "true"
    },
    {
      "question": "Getting involved in politics includes all except",
      "options": [
        "Be card carrying member",
        "Get voter’s card",
        "Get registered into political party",
        "Join electoral body"
      ],
      "answer":"Be card carrying member"
    },
    {
      "question": "Politics is not a do or die affair",
      "options": [
        "Yes",
        "No",
        "A and B",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "Yes"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is the purpose for sending God’s word?",
      "options": [
        "Direction and show ways",
        "Mislead",
        "Destroy",
        "Blindfolded"
      ],
      "answer": "Direction and show ways"
    },
    {
      "question": "Jesus followed suit and we must also follow in his",
      "options": [
        "Shoes",
        "Steps",
        "Ways",
        "Ideas"
      ],
      "answer": "Steps"
    },
    {
      "question": "The mystery of iniquity is the working of _________ in the world?",
      "options": [
        "Diligent",
        "Law abiding",
        "Lawlessness",
        "Spirit"
      ],
      "answer": "Lawlessness"
    },
    {
      "question": "The idea behind the book of Colossians 3:10 is to?",
      "options": [
        "Put on the new man",
        "Put on the new spirit",
        "Put on the new idea",
        "Put on the Holy Spirit"
      ],
      "answer" : "Put on the new man"
    },
    {
      "question": "To please God is accomplished by ______?",
      "options": [
        "Love",
        "Holy Spirit",
        "Faith",
        "Jesus Christ"
      ],
      "answer": "Faith"
    },
    {
      "question": "The currency of believers in this world is ______?",
      "options": [
        "Holy Spirit",
        "Faith",
        "Love",
        "Prayer"
      ],
      "answer": "Prayer"
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the Bible passage for lesson 14?",
      "options": [
        "Hebrews 12:3-11",
        "Hebrews 12:12-15",
        "Hebrews 13:3-11",
        "Hebrews 11:3-11"
      ],
      "answer": "Hebrews 11:3-11"
    },
    {
      "question": "______ is one of the Bible characters who listened to voices?",
      "options": [
        "Samuel",
        "Old prophets",
        "David",
        "Joel"
      ],
      "answer" : "Samuel"
    },
    {
      "question": "The voice of God comes with ______?",
      "options": [
        "Love",
        "Power",
        "Faith",
        "Trembling"
      ],
      "answer": "Love"
    },
    {
      "question": "Lesson 16 Topic is?",
      "options": [
        "Significant of voices",
        "Divine leading and guidance 1",
        "Divine leading and Guidance 2",
        "Mystery of faith"
      ],
      "answer": "Divine leading and guidance 1"
    },
    {
      "question": "Dream can come from your thought",
      "options": [
        "True",
        "False",
        "A and B",
        "None of the above"
      ],
      "answer": "False"
    },
    {
      "question": "One of the factors that influence our choices highlighted in James 1:19 and 1 Samuel 25:10 is?",
      "options": [
        "Good Vision",
        "Self-Control",
        "Prayer",
        "Knowledge"
      ],
      "answer": "Self-Control"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following reasons for Fasting is outlined in Isaiah 40:30-31?",
      "options": [
        "Spiritual Strength",
        "Repentance from sinful ways",
        "Spiritual hunger",
        "Demonstration of love"
      ],
      "answer" : "Spiritual Strength"
    },
    {
      "question": "The reason for fasting is _______ to you",
      "options": [
        "Dependent",
        "Independent",
        "According",
        "Wholly"
      ],
      "answer": "wholly"
    },
    {
      "question": "Lesson 17 topic is?",
      "options": [
        "Reason for Fasting",
        "Benefits of Fasting",
        "Divine Leading and Guidance 2",
        "Mystery of Faith"
      ],
      "answer" : "Divine Leading and Guidance 2"
    },
    {
      "question": "According to Luke 18vs 1, “And he Spake a parable unto them this end, that men ought always to pray and not to faint.” This is the memory verse for Lesson ",
      "options": [
        "20",
        "21",
        "22",
        "23"
      ],
      "answer": "21"
    },
    {
      "question": "The result of vain imagination is  ",
      "options": [
        "Immorality",
        "Ingratitude",
        "Spiritual blindness",
        "Inordinate affection."
      ],
      "answer": "Spiritual blindness"
    },
  ]
}